那么，我们如何在我们的程序中实现服务呢？
So, how would we use a service to
幸运的是，我们已经完成了大部分的工作
implement our application? Fortunately, we've already done most
我们这里有个Content Provider，它里面有
of the work. We have a content provider
Content Notifier。Content Notifier会通知
with a content notifier that will notify our
Content Observers。这个FetchWeatherTask和UI在运行中完全独立的。
content observers. Our FetchWeatherTask already runs completely independently
还算不错！
of our UI. Good on us. Now, we
那么，我们现在可以用一下之前Rato提到过的
can make use of that Intent Service that
Intent Service。仅需要稍作修改，
Rato mentioned earlier. With just a few small
我们就能用Intent Service来替换
changes, we can get our code working,
FetchWeatherTask。
with an Intent Service, instead of with our
首先创建一个新的package
Fetch Weather task. To start, let's create a
这里存放服务的源码
new package for our service. [SOUND] Then we'll
然后我们在package中添加一个java类源码文件，该类继承IntentService
add a new Java class in that package that extends inside Service. We hit Ctrl+I
这里再次使用Ctrl+I快捷键来自动添加需要重写的抽象方法
to once again, add the required abstract method.
然后使用Ctrl+O来添加构造方法。
And Ctrl+O in order to add the constructor.
由于Service属于Android的基本组件，所以你懂的，需要在Manifest中进行注册
Since the service is an Android component, you guessed it, it needs to be in the
来吧！让我们实现SunshineService的代码，并在ForecastFragment里进行调用。
manifest. Okay, let's do this. Let's finish implementing the SunshineService
我们可以通过startService方法，并传递一个intent对象来启动一个服务。
and call it from ForecastFragment. You can start a service using an intent with
要是掌握了如何使用显式声明的Intents，会对实现该部分代码很有帮助。
the StartService method. It will help to remember how to use explicit intents.